Guide to the Rice University Faculty Council records, 1919-2006 UA 106
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Rice University Faculty Council records
1919-1993
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Rice University. Faculty Council.
UA 106
57.5 Linear Feet (50 boxes)
Minutes, election information, and correspondence of the Rice University Faculty Council.
Historical Sketch
The original Rice University Faculty Council was formed as an expansion of the Executive Committee in l959. The members of this group consisted of the President (chairman), the Provost, the Dean of the Institute, the Dean of Humanities, the Dean of Engineering, and six members elected by the Faculty. A re-organization took place again, in 1971, in conjunction with the formation of a University Council. At this point changes were made in the Faculty Council's membership and its mission. Membership now consisted of eight Faculty members elected to serve on the University Council along with eight other Faculty members elected to serve only on the Faculty Council. Their mission was re-defined to initiate studies and examine proposals submitted by faculty members. Most other University matters were to be dealt with by the University Committees and the University Council. In fact, this change shifted greater responsibility to the newly formed University Council and gave the Faculty Council the mission of the now defunct Committee on University Welfare.
Scope and Contents
The contents of this record group include minutes, election information, and correspondence of the Rice University Faculty Council, and were drawn from several sources including Secretary of the Faculty (Robert L. Patten), President Pitzer's Papers, Vandiver and Hackerman Papers. Box 1 includes all of the records under the original format of the Faculty Council and early pre-Faculty Council materials from 1919-1925. Boxes 3 and 4 under the newer format. The organization of these files is chronological and the contents are primarily the minutes of meetings and agendas, with some correspondence and election information. The record groups most closely related to this one are Faculty Meeting Minutes, University Council, and Committee on University Welfare. Formats include photocopies and mimeographed sheets.
Access Restrictions
Permission of the current Secretary of the Faculty required to view files or make copies. Permission in writing or by email from the Secretary of the Faculty must be sent to the Woodson Research Center. Call the Woodson Research Center for more information.
Conditions Governing Access
Stored off-site at the Library Service Center. Please request this material via woodson@rice.edu or call 713-348-2586.
Acquisition Information
These records were transferred to the Woodson Research Center from the Secretary of the Faculty and the President's Office. Date(s) received: 9/74; 5/81; 4/82; 7/8/88; 7/89; 1/93, 2006
Index Terms
Subjects
Universities and colleges
Document Types
photocopies; minutes (administrative records)
Subjects (Corporations)
Rice University. Faculty Council.
- Series I: 1919-1970, 244482
  - 1919-1925, 244503 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee, 1946-59 [pre-Faculty Council], 244502 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee, 1947-49 [pre-Faculty Council], 244501 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1959-60, 244500 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1960-61, 244499 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1961-62, 244498 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 1962-63, 244497 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1963-64, 244496 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 1964-65 (1/2), 244495 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 1964-65 (2/2), 244494 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - American Council on Education Statement (1964), 244493 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 1965-66 (1/2), 244492 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 1965-66 (2/2), 244491 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 1966-67 (1/2), 244490 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 1966-67 (2/2), 244489 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - 1967-68 (1/2), 244488 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - 1967-68 (2/2), 244487 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - 1968-69 (1/2), 244486 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - 1968-69 (2/2), 244485 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - 1969-70, 244484 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Memos (1969-1973), 244483 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Series II: 1970-1995, 244342
  - 1970-71 (1/2), 244481 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - 1970-71 (2/2), 244480 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - 1971-72, 244479 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Consumer Price Index (1971-1983), 244478 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - 1972-73 (1/2), 244477 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - 1972-73 (2/2), 244476 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - 1973-74 (1/4), 244475 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - 1973-74 (2/4), 244474 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - 1973-74 (3/4), 244473 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - 1973-74 (4/4), 244472 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Elections (October 1974), 244471 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Salary Subcommittee (1973-74), 244470 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - 1974-75 (1/2), 244469 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - 1974-75 (2/2), 244468 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Council: Salaries and Compensation Miscellaneous (1974-1984), 244467 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Memos (1974-1977), 244466 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Elections (April 1975), 244465 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Elections (October 1975, 244464 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Notes and Drafts of Minutes (1975-76), 244463 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - 1975-76, 244462 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Salary Ranking Worksheets (1975-1982), 244461 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Elections (April 1976), 244460 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 1976-77 (1/2), 244459 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - 1976-77 (2/2), 244458 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - 1977-78, 244457 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Elections (May 1977), 244456 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - 1978-79, 244455 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Presentation Materials (1978), 244454 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Memos (1978-79), 244453 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - 1979-80, 244452 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - 1980-81, 244451 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Elections 1980-81, 244450 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Memos (1980-1985), 244449 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Policies (1980-1998), 244448 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - 1981-82, 244447 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - 1982-83 (1/2), 244446 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 1982-83 (2/2), 244445 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Council Compensation Committee- MIT Survey Data (1982/83- 1990/91) (1/2), 244444 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Council Compensation Committee- MIT Survey Data (1982/83- 1990/91) (2/2), 244443 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - 1983-84, 244442 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Council: Salaries and Compensation (1983-1986), 244441 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - 1984-85, 244440 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Bureau of Labor Statistics (1984-85), 244439 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 1985-86, 244438 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Salary/Compensation Reports etc (1985), 244437 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Council Salary/Compensation Committee (1985-1986), 244436 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Council: Salaries and Compensation (1985-1986), 244435 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Membership (1985-86 to 1988-89), 244434 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Bylaws (1986-1988), 244433 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Minutes, Memos, Correspondence (1986-1987), 244432 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Council: Salary and Benefits Subcommittee (1986-1987), 244431 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Memos (1986-1987), 244430 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Compensation Committee (1987-88-89), 244429 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Dead Week/Final Exams (1987-88-89), 244428 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Elections and Appointments (1987-88-89), 244427 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Faculty and Board (1987-1988), 244426 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Council Compensation Committee MIT Surveys (1987-1988), 244425 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Retirement (1987-1988), 244424 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Minutes, Memos, Correspondence (1987-1988), 244423 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Financial Aid- Student Athletes (1987-1988), 244422 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Sexual Harassment Policy (1987-1988), 244421 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - University Standing Committees (1987-1988), 244420 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Council: Compensation Committee (1988-1989), 244419 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Memos (1988-1989), 244418 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Minutes, Memos, Correspondence (1988-1989), 244417 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence and Memos (1989-1990) (1/2), 244416 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence and Memos (1989-1990) (2/2), 244415 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Proceedings (1989-1990), 244414 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Tenure and Ethics Committee (1989-1990), 244413 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Commission on Women (1989-1990), 244412 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Members and Elections (1989-1990), 244411 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Governance Committee (1989-1990), 244410 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Outside Activities of Faculty (1989-1990), 244409 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Research Misconduct (1989-1990), 244408 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Tuition Waiver (1989-1990), 244407 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Tenure, Leave of Absence etc (1989-1990), 244406 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Standing Committees (1989-1990), 244405 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Honor System (1989-1990), 244404 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Minutes (1989-1990), 244403 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Committees (1990-2000), 244402 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, Memos, Minutes (proceedings) (1990-1991), 244401 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Faculty Council Compensation Report -1990/1991- DATA, 244400 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Memos (1990-1994), 244399 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Athletics Committee (1991-1997), 244398 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - College Masters Committee (1991-1997), 244397 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Committees (1991-1997), 244396 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Computer Committee (1991-1997), 244395 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Environmental Health and Safety Committee (1991-1997), 244394 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Examinations and Standing Committee (1991-1997), 244393 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Council (1991-92); Compensation Committee Reports (1990-91), 244392 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Council Bylaws (1991-2003), 244391 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Council Report on Salaries and Compensation (1991-1996), 244390 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Council: Salaries and Compensation (1991-1992), 244389 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Handbook (1991-1998), 244388 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Handbook Committee: Memos/Miscellaneous (1991-1998), 244387 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Graduate Council Committee (1991-1996), 244386 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Library Committee (1991-1999), 244385 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Marshals Committee (1991-1999), 244384 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Minutes (proceedings) (1991-1992), 244383 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Presidents Lectures Committee (1991-2000), 244382 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - University Review Board Committee (1991-1996), 244381 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - 1992-1993 (1/2), 244380 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - 1992-1993 (2/2), 244379 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Athletics (1992), 244378 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Benefits (1992), 244377 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Athletics Reports (1992-1993), 244376 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence/Memos (1992), 244375 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Council: Salaries and Compensation (1992-1993), 244374 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Admission Committee (1993-2000), 244373 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - External (1993), 244372 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Faculty and Staff Benefits Committee (1993-2000), 244371 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Minutes (1993/94-1995/96), 244370 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - "Academe" Economic Report (1994-1995), 244369 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Agendas (1994-1995), 244368 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Committee Assignments (1994-2000), 244367 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Committee on Athletics (1994), 244366 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Curriculum Committee (1994-1996), 244365 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Handbook: Brown University (1994), 244364 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Handbook: Emory University (1994), 244363 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Meetings (1994-1995), 244362 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Affirmative Action Committee (1995-1997), 244361 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Bylaws Revision (1995), 244360 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Committee Handouts/Bylaws (1995-1997), 244359 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Council Bylaws/Miscellaneous (1995-1997), 244358 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- September 12, 1995, 244357 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- October 18, 1995, 244356 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- October 23, 1995, 244355 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- November 16, 1995, 244354 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- December 12, 1995, 244353 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Council: Report on Salaries and Compensation (1995-1996), 244352 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Council: Salaries and Compensation (1995-1996), 244351 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Handbook: Chronicle of Higher Education Article (1995), 244350 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Handbook Committee: Miscellaneous (1995-1998), 244349 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Handbook- Duke University (1995), 244348 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Handbook: "Recommended Institutional Regulations on Academic Freedom and Tenure" (1995), 244347 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Governance/Bylaws- Duke University (1995), 244346 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Haskell Correspondence Speaker (1995-1996), 244345 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous (1995-1996), 244344 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Scholarships and Awards Committee (1995), 244343 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Series III: 1996-2006, 243943
  - AD HOC Curriculum Committee (1996-1998), 244341 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Articles of Incorporation/Amendments (1996), 244340 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Charges to Committees (1996-1997), 244339 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Committees (1996), 244338 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Faculty (1996-1997), 244337 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- January 26, 1996, 244336 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- February 26, 1996, 244335 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- March 22, 1996, 244334 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- April 15, 1996, 244333 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- June 26, 1996, 244332 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- September 26, 1996, 244331 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- October 28, 1996, 244330 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- November 25, 1996, 244329 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- December 13, 1996, 244328 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Council: Salaries and Compensation (1996-1997), 244327 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Faculty Handbook: Amended and Restated Bylaws (1996), 244326 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Faculty Handbook: Amherst College (1996), 244325 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Faculty Handbook: Brandeis University (1996), 244324 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Faculty Handbook: Cal Tech (1996), 244323 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Faculty Handbook: Carleton College (1996), 244322 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Faculty Handbook: Columbia University (1996), 244321 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Faculty Handbook: Cornell University (1996), 244320 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Handbook Distribution List (1996), 244319 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Handbook: Duke University (1996) (1/2), 244318 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Handbook: Duke University (1996) (2/2), 244317 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Handbook: Princeton University (1996), 244316 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Handbook: Reed College (1996), 244315 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Handbook: Stanford University (1996), 244314 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Handbook: Southern Methodist University (1996), 244313 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Handbook: Tulane University (1996), 244312 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Handbook: University of California (1996), 244311 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Handbook: University of Chicago (1996), 244310 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Handbook: University of Houston (1996), 244309 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Handbook: University of Illinois at Chicago (1996), 244308 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Handbook: University of Pennsylvania (1996), 244307 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Handbook: University of Pittsburgh (1996), 244306 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Handbook: University of Rochester (1996), 244305 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Handbook: University of Texas at Houston (1996), 244304 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Handbook: Vanderbilt University (1996), 244303 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Handbook: Yale University (1996), 244302 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Honor System (1996), 244301 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Letter to Faculty and Responses (1996), 244300 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Meeting Schedules (1996), 244299 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Minutes and Proceedings (1996/1997-1999/2000), 244298 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - NROTC Committee (1996), 244297 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Promotions and Tenure Committee (1996), 244296 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Questions for Interviews (1996), 244295 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Rice Vision (1996), 244294 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Role of Faculty in the Honor System (1996), 244293 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Standing Committees (1996-1997), 244292 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Student Position Information (1996-1997), 244291 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - University Charter and Bylaws (1996), 244290 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Appointments/Promotion/Tenure (1997), 244289 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Department Chair Responses (1997), 244288 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Committee Chair Responses (1997), 244287 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Committee on Committees (Spring 1997), 244286 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - External (1997), 244285 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- January 27, 1997, 244284 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- February 17, 1997, 244283 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- March 14, 1997, 244282 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- April 8, 1997, 244281 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- May 1, 1997, 244280 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- May 15, 1997, 244279 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- September 3, 1997, 244278 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- September 16, 1997, 244277 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- October 7, 1997, 244276 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- October 23, 1997, 244275 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- November 11, 1997, 244274 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- November 12, 1997, 244273 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- November 25, 1997, 244272 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - FHC: Memos/Miscellaneous (1997), 244271 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Letters to President and Provost (1997), 244270 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Mail outs (1997), 244269 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Supporting Materials (1997-1998), 244268 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Undergraduate Curriculum Committee (1997-1998), 244267 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Appeals/Grievances Committee (1998), 244266 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Committee on Committees (1998-1999), 244265 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - "Computing, Telecommunication and Multimedia Services" (1998-1999), 244264 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- January 16, 1998, 244263 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- February 3, 1998, 244262 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- February 10, 1998, 244261 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- March 10, 1998, 244260 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- March 24, 1998, 244259 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- April 5, 1998, 244258 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- April 7, 1998, 244257 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- April 21, 1998, 244256 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- April 27, 1998, 244255 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- April 28, 1998, 244254 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- June 1, 1998, 244253 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- September 2, 1998, 244252 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- September 21, 1998, 244251 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- October 22, 1998, 244250 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- November 10, 1998, 244249 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- November 20, 1998, 244248 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Handbook Committee: Policies (1998-1999), 244247 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Handbook Committee: "Yale-Freedom of Expression" (1998-1999), 244246 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Handbook: "Academic Freedom references" (1998), 244245 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Handbook: "Other" (1998), 244244 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Handbook: Policies (1998-1999), 244243 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Gillis Appt. Letters: Committees (1998-1999), 244242 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Handouts- June 1, 1998 FC Meeting, 244241 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Memos/Correspondence (1998-1999), 244240 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Database—Miscellaneous (1/2) (1999-2000), 244239 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Database—Miscellaneous (2/2) (1995-1998), 244238 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Council: Bylaws (1999-2004), 244237 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Council Committees (1999-2001), 244236 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Council Committee on Committees (various) (1999-2001), 244235 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Council Election Coordination (1999), 244234 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- February 11, 1999, 244233 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- April 27, 1999, 244232 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Council Meeting- May 7, 1999, 244231 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Council Policy (1999), 244230 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Handbook Committee: First Meeting (1999), 244229 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Handbook (1999), 244228 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Handbook: Revisions/Policy (1999), 244227 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Memos/Faculty Handbook (1999) (1/2), 244226 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Memos/Faculty Handbook (1999) (2/2), 244225 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous (1999), 244224 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Promotion and Tenure Guidelines (1999), 244223 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Salary Equity Committee (1999-2000), 244222 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Undergraduate Teaching Committee (1999-2000), 244221 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Calendar (2000-2004) (1/2), 244220 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Calendar (2000-2004) (2/2), 244219 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Committees (2000-2001), 244218 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - CONFIDENTIAL (2000), 244217 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Copyright/Intellectual Property (2000-2001), 244216 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Database/Records (2000-2001), 244215 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Dismissals/Financial Exigency (2000-2001), 244214 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Council (2000-2001), 244213 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Council (2000-2001), 244212 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Council Agendas (2000-2002) (1/2), 244211 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Council Agendas (2000-2002) (2/2), 244210 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Council Compensation (2000-2004), 244209 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Council: Faculty Senate (2000-2002), 244208 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Council: Miscellaneous (2000-2001), 244207 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Jones School (2000-2001), 244206 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Minutes and Proceedings (2000), 244205 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Salary and Comp. Subcommittee (2000-2004), 244204 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Agendas/Miscellaneous (2001-2002), 244203 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Agendas, President/Provost (2002-2002), 244202 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Athletics (2001-2002), 244201 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Committee Service Prefs (2001-2002) (1/2), 244200 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Committee Service Prefs (2002-2002) (2/2), 244199 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Compensation Committee (2001-2002), 244198 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - CONFIDENTIAL (2001-2003), 244197 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Faculty Council Committee on Committees (2001-2002), 244196 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Curriculum (2001-2002), 244195 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Elections (2001-2002), 244194 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Election 2001 (Spring) (call for nomination; petition), 244193 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Election—Fall 2001 (August-September), 244192 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Election of Members to University Council and Faculty Council (2001), 244191 (Box 28, Folder 7)